seriously
you can
all you need is a couple of decent
cameras two nice lenses nothing fancy i
use the panasonic 25mm for wide and a
samyang 85mm for close-up and a light
find a spot to shoot your interviewees
and set up your two angles play around
with the light until you get that
the triangle thing on your cheek you
know the the the the
russell brandt thing the that
you'll probably need some muslin too to
lift the shadows uh or a bed sheet
and boom
pole you need good audio okay this is
not a suggestion it's looking good
record it no next you'll need you need
some b-roll because staring at this for
the whole thing ain't okay then grab
some stock footage to make it seem like
we had more than 75 to work with and
you're up to the final part it's my
favorite part
this is where you're gonna add that
netflix spice i'm talking drone shots a
single piano key somewhere a timeline um
dramatic titles and of course some bass
drops
you blend it all together and you get
this
um i can remember it like it was
yesterday
because it was
monday the 23rd
[Music]
it's actually my day off work
and i start every day the same when i
have a day off
and that was 11 22 am
the last time i saw my jam on toast
[Music]
sometime between
me going to the loo
and then getting back
to the kitchen
somebody ate my jam on toast
[Music]
there were only two other people in the
house when the crime took place because
it is a crime my brother max
and my mother jan both of whom deny
having any
involvement
[Music]
why would i
i would never
you know i'm his mother you know i
didn't know what to do but you know
luckily i didn't have to go through this
alone
[Music]
uh yeah
i'm andrew mccloskey
and i'm a retired
police detective
i actually lived next door to the
wilsons
and overheard the altercation that took
place
after the incident had occurred
[Music]
and i just came over to see everything
was all right
immediately it was like what is going on
here
i'm still in disbelief it was like they
were mocking me
you know oh we ate your toast
but we left you the crust that we know
you hate
we're dealing with a truly sick
individual this is ridiculous they both
know i don't do crust i mean who does
just lead to christ
think about it i'm two parts jam
[Music]
the culprit will be called i love butter
there are only two other people in the
house
yes
this whole
situation this this scenario
is totally ridiculous
um but i'm not going to sit here
and
lie to you
and say that i'm not heavily invested in
how this pans out
[Music]
you