foreign
about Vice news remember Vice news
I know they don't matter
I allowed them to come and do a piece on
me in the war room
about seven months ago now
I knew it would be eight piece of course
I'm a professional but I also knew
anyone with a brain would see through
the hit Peaks and see the beauty of the
worm and want to join so I allowed them
to come to a hit piece
and then
I got interviewed by Piers Morgan I'll
look for calling
it's our friends from Vice but he can
wait
then I interviewed by Piers Morgan and
he came at me hard and all of the
comments are saying bro takes a g The
Matrix tries to tell the world that
everyone hates me but the truth is
everyone actually loves me so when peers
tried to come for me hard expecting to
be a hero he was actually attacked and
he felt like oops I made a mistake which
stopped Vice releasing their hit piece
because they called me and said hey
don't call him
he called me that hey we want to film
some more we feel like we didn't get the
other side of the story basically we
want to undo the hit piece and do the
fair journalism we were supposed to do
in the first place because now we
realize making a hit piece on you
doesn't work out well for us
then I went to jail because I'm Matrix
attacked and they thought ah he's a bad
guy now we can do a hit piece and they
released a hit piece and nobody believed
it just like I said everyone saw through
it salt was garbage to the point where
Vice had to turn the comments off
because everyone was insulting them they
even falsely edited me stuttering what
have you ever seen me stutter on any
video ever to try and make me look
frustrated like I've been caught out by
this dork called Matt
so they released the hit piece and it
was totally detrimental for them nobody
believed them bombed their reputation
even worse Vice used to be something and
now they're completely off the deep end
nobody gives a [ __ ] about them complete
Matrix propaganda
so then I get released from jail
and now Matt from Vice is begging me
begging me for another interview
calling me every day begging me
please please please
so I've decided because I'm such a nice
man most people have
an organization anymore but I'm so nice
I'm gonna have a conversation with Vice
news we're gonna talk today
we're going to talk to Matt let me
message him
again I said an instruction
again
like a little dog
so wait for Matt to call us and we're
gonna hear what Matt has to say about
the fact that they were dishonest
and they weren't particularly good at oh
look
again please Mr
Geeks
well if it isn't Mac
Andrew hey
Mr honest journalism
it's a shame nobody else thinks of you
that way Matt that's why you have to
- turn off the comments on your little
- video
hey are you at home
congrats on your being released under uh
house arrest thank you
what do you think is is next
well
it's a beautiful reality Matt
it's a beautiful life and I'm clearly
one of God's chosen ones
and I'm here to spread a positive
message and continue with my mission
to prevent the degeneracy which is
purported by organizations like Vice
drug taking
and other forms of pornography a bunch
of other stuff you want are involved in
I'm here to combat it I'm going to lead
people to the truth and to the light
and we're all going to be better people
have a better Society for that and I
think you learned that
when you turn the comments off in your
little video
that most people understand I'm a Force
for good and that hit pieces don't
really work because
you've lost all credibility the
mainstream Matrix mechanisms of the
media
unfortunately for you
is that is that your excuse
I want to see whether you were up for
doing another interview not revise but
for the BBC
why would you want to interview me I'm a
- bad person I thought according to your
- little uh story
I just tried to report both sides of
every story so oh you do both sides is
that how you think you work
well that includes your side as well so
you know it was obviously difficult to
interview you while you were in jail now
you're out you know we can actually have
a chance to hear your side of things
problem is Matt
everyone on the planet wants to
interview me
so the question is why would I choose
you when I have unlimited offers from
people who are far more successful and
better than you at the jaw
because I'd be doing and I'm not trying
to disrespect you I'm being honest I'd
be doing you a favor like Matt
what's your last name Shane
that name didn't matter until it was
Associated to mine you do an interview
with me you matter for a little bit but
I can do an interview with anyone
so why would I do an interview with you
and this isn't genuinely a question it's
not an insult I'm actually asking you
why I would choose you
when I have unlimited offers on the
table
because we have a history
we have a history of you doing dishonest
journalism on me so I would choose you
interesting
any journalist that you speak to is
going to
ask you the Sim similar questions the
ones I asked you I have no problem with
your questions
the reason the reason that I want to do
an interview with you and of course you
can do an interview with anyone you want
and you know that's entirely your choice
I'm just you know one of the many people
asking you I guess but we have a history
and we got cut short last time and there
are still unanswered questions that I
want to put to you I can only tell you
why I want to interview you you know
ultimately it is your choice
it is my choice isn't it I get to choose
which reporter in the world all these
reporters who want to say bad things
about me I get to choose which report
are on the planet gets to become
relevant via proxy because I am the most
relevant person and I get to do the
charitable Act of allowing somebody to
sit next to me and ask me questions
it's kind of interesting I need to think
heavily about it I can't just give out
such a fantastic opportunity to
disingenuous nobodies it's something I
need to think about do you work for the
BBC now or do you work for yourself
I'm an independent contractor but it has
to be broadcast somewhere and I think
the BBC is is where it would go
but one thing I would say though is
uh I spoke to the sartorial shooter and
he said that one of the things you might
want is the chance to film it and record
it yourself
Oh you mean so you can't edit in
stutters like you did with Vice to
pretend I was stuttering when I was
answering questions is that what is that
why
I don't know what your friends yes you
do Matt the algorithm to make you become
more famous and more viral I'm not an
expert on algorithms for social media
platforms I do not have most of them
installed on my phone I cannot control a
15 year old Singaporean decides to do
when he chops me up and calls me names I
can't control that and I wouldn't try to
when you search for Europe and I
wouldn't try to when you search for your
name in Google what are the associated
terms why then of the Romanian police
said the investigation is ongoing I'm
not sure where you got that information
from I'm not sure who said it is there
some kind of procedure that must be
completed I don't know there has been a
lot of bad sure that must be completed I
don't know there has been a lot of bad
I can't control that and I wouldn't try
to when you search for your sure that
- must be completed I don't know there has
- been a lot of bad
let's be honest with each other we have
a history we're friends now don't lie
startups were edited in to try and make
it look like you stumped me with your
- asinine questions which of course is
- absolutely impossible
what you might be referring to is
sometimes we cut to b-roll of someone's
face when we're editing an interview
because you know we spoke for almost an
hour but it gets cut down to only a few
minutes so there are going to be some
edits and we are going to cut to your
face at some point
- um you did you dishonestly edited okay
- we agree
I would say we don't dishonestly edit it
but the idea that we would just release
a you know an hour long unedited entity
it doesn't really make sense right
because of the whole documentary is only
45 minutes so anyway but the point is I
can't stop you filming
in your own home you know releasing
whatever you want to release editing it
however you want to edit it you know I
can't stop you doing that so if that's
what you want to do then you obviously
can do it and then you know when people
say
oh Matt you've unfairly edited this or
whatever you can say well here's the the
full unedited you're right version
you're right I can film our interview to
protect myself from your dishonest
journalism I appreciate that thank you
I'm gonna think about it Matt because
I'm the one who matters here I can sit
down with [ __ ] peer with
Big Bird Oscar the Grouch I can sit down
with anybody it'll be the most viewed
podcast or interview in the world so I'm
gonna think about it that's true would
you would you bring me a box of
chocolates
I can bring you a box of chocolates
if you promise to bring me a box of
chocolates that will increase your
chances and I'll give you an answer
- within 24 hours but you have to promise
- me Matt don't lie to me
I'll I'll check with my superiors
whether I can send you a box of
chocolates well then you check with your
boss you go into your boss's room and
ask if you're allowed to spend
a large portion of your salary on a five
pound box of chocolates and you let me
know and if you can then I will strongly
consider allowing you
the opportunity to speak with me
are you asking all the journalists to
bring you a box of chocolates you let me
know about the chocolates man have a
nice day